module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What movie won the Oscar for Best Picture in 2018?', 
    a: 'Ladybird',
    b: 'Shape of Water',
    c: 'Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, MO',
    d: 'Kevin & Marion\'s First Dance Vid',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who headlined the Superbowl Halftime Show in 2018?', 
    a: 'Bruno Mars',
    b: 'Coldplay',
    c: 'Lady Gaga',
    d: 'Justin Timberlake',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Netflix show premiered this year?', 
    a: 'Ozark',
    b: 'Altered Carbon',
    c: 'Atypical',
    d: 'Mindhunter',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was People\'s Sexiest Man Alive this year?', 
    a: 'Idris Elba',
    b: 'Blake Shelton',
    c: 'Troy Acosta',
    d: 'Hugh Jackman',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which song won the Grammy for Best Recoord in 2018?', 
    a: '24k Magic by Bruno Mars',
    b: 'Humble by Kendrick Lamar',
    c: 'Despacito by Luis Fonsi',
    d: 'Wonderwall performed by Ryan Garner',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who won Outstanding Lead Actress in a drama at the Emmy\'s in 2018?', 
    a: 'Claire Foy (The Crown)',
    b: 'Elizabeth Moss (The Handmaid\'s Tale)',
    c: 'Sandra Oh (Killing Eve)',
    d: 'Jane Degen (Dealing w/ The Pod)',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who won the Superbowl in 2018?', 
    a: 'New England Patriots',
    b: 'Philadelphia Eagles',
    c: 'Los Angeles Rams',
    d: 'New York Giants',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who won the World Cup in 2018?', 
    a: 'Croatia',
    b: 'Brazil',
    c: 'Germany',
    d: 'France',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played rescuer Jonas Taylor in the 2018 sci-fi film, The Meg?', 
    a: 'Dwayne Johnson',
    b: 'Jonathan Coffman',
    c: 'Jason Statham',
    d: 'Nicolas Cage',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the global audience size of Prince Harry & Meghan Markle\'s wedding?', 
    a: '7.3 million',
    b: '1.9 billion',
    c: '3.1 billion',
    d: '3.3 billion',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];